<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mazdoor App</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="enter_your_password">Enter your password</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_me">About me</string>
    <string name="about_project"><b>Mazdoor App </b>  is basically for the community so that all the community comes together and provide some services any buy any type of services
        <b>Mazdoor App</b>  has three modules.\n\n   <b> Admin</b>\n\n   <b>Skill Provider</b>\n\n   <b>Skill user</b>\n\n
        <u><b>Admin</b></u>\n\nThis module is controlling the provider verification and the procedure how a provider can sell his/her services.When ever a provider is registered in <b>Skill Provider Module</b> and after profile section the request is submitted to <b> Admin</b> and the <b> Skill Provider</b> have to contact the admin through whatsapp for account approval. After the providers approval admin can approve and his profile will be activated and is shown in <b>Skill User Module</b>\n\n
        <u><b>Skill Provider</b></u>\n\Skill provider Module starts from authentication of the provider and the authentication is done by using <b>Firebase Database</b> after authentication the provider can make his profile and all the instruction is provided in the app. After profile submission the data is added to Firebase database and until his approval we are showing how to approve his profile by admin.He can contact Admin and register himself by paying registration fee so that he can sell his service.After approval of his profile his profile is shown in <b>Skill User Module</b> along with his details.\n\n
        <u><b>Skill User</b></u> \n\nThe authentication is done by using Shared preference local Storage of Android. In Login Page a layout appears to contact admin so that admin will provide password of user app.After authentication the user is redirected and some instruction are shown that how to use the app.In services section all the provider categories are shown.He can pick any category like Carpenter,and a list of carpenters will appear from them he can choose any one of them and contact through his phone number and track his location.    </string>
    <string name="lookin_for">If you’re looking to book the best  service to help you out around the house, look no further than <b>Mazdoor App</b>. We know you’ve got a never-ending list of odd jobs that need doing around your home. However, with the demands of work and family, it’s so hard to find the time to tackle them all. When you use the <b>Mazdoor App</b> app , you’ll be connected with local <b>Mazdoor App</b> professionals who can take care of this work for you. In addition to freeing up your time for the more important things in life, booking a person through the <b>Mazdoor App</b> platform will give you the security of knowing that things are being handled by an expert. If the sight of a hammer or screwdriver fills you with anxiety and you’d rather leave things to a professional, the <b>Mazdoor App</b> platform is ready to help.</string>

</resources>